Tomoyuki Fujii

Full-stack developer

Vancouver, BC, Canada

TEL: (236) 838-7694 / E-mail: mjr01300828@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Tomoyuki Fujii / GitHub: Tomoyuki 3001 / Portfolio: Tomoyuki Fujii

Summary

Junior Full-stack Developer with 2 years of experience in web development and a passion for user experience and interaction design and strength in creative and strategic thinking. Learning and growing as a developer are important to me and I am excellent at working in teams and enjoy collaboration.

Technical Specifications

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, Node.js, React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, MySQL, MongoDB, GitHub

Projects

The school website - December 2022 Website / GitHub

Students and instructors can see their own profile page, make new appointments, and make their own schedule with a booking system.

Technical specifications: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Postgres

The post record app - August 2022 Website / GitHub

Like Twitter, you can create accounts and posts and remember them, with a limit of 140 characters, and you can see when a post is created in the past.

Technical specifications: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js

The bank tracker app - September 2022 Website / GitHub

An expense tracker app allows you to track and categorize your spending.

Technical specifications: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js

Education

Cornerstone International Community College - January 2022 - Present

Web development diploma

Tokai University - April 2014 - March 2018Bachelor of Political Science and Economics

Employment

Tellext Inc. - Canada / March 2023 ~ Present

Full-stack developer

• Creating websites with WordPress and programming languages.

Dunlop Sports Marketing Ltd. - Japan / April 2018 - June 2021

Sales Representative

- Customer information and budget management.
- Create proposals to acquire new clients and increase sales of existing clients.
- Devising new products based on information from customers.